Aaron Green has 72 hours to get a rock star from London to L.A. Pray for him.
Get Him to the Greek is a adventure, comedy, music
film directed by Nicholas Stoller.
Pinnacle records has the perfect plan to get their sinking company back on track: a comeback concert in LA
featuring Aldous Snow, a fading rockstar who has dropped off the radar in recent years.
Record company intern Aaron Green is faced with the monumental task of bringing his idol,
out of control rock star Aldous Snow, back to LA for his comeback show.
Aaron Green, played by Jonah Hill.
Aldous Snow, played by Russell Brand.
Jackie Q, played by Rose Byrne.
Daphne Binks, played by Elisabeth Moss.
African Child in Video, played by Tyler McKinney.
Zöe Salmon, played by Zoe Salmon.
Get Him to the Greek is a 2010 American comedy film written, produced, and directed by Nicholas Stoller that serves as a spin-off sequel to
Forgetting Sarah Marshall (2008), and reunites director Stoller with stars Russell Brand and Jonah Hill and producer Judd Apatow.
Brand reprises his role as character Aldous Snow while Hill plays an entirely new character,
Aaron Green, and Elisabeth Moss, Rose Byrne, Sean Combs, and Colm Meaney also star.
The film was released on June 4, 2010, received generally positive reviews from
critics, and grossed $95 million against its $40 million budget.
The film explores themes of london, england, concert, musician,
los angeles, california, aftercreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted.